<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--*********************************************************************
 * @author	Kingsley U. Uwode II, contractor via Robert Half Technologies
 * @since	May 28 2015
 * @link	mailto:kingzmeadow@hotmail.com
 *
 * step_07:
 * Upsell (*.html view companion file)
 *-->
 
<step id="07">
    <page_title>
        <english><![CDATA[Register now and SAVE! ]]></english>
<french><![CDATA[Inscrivez-vous maintenant et SAVE!]]></french>
    </page_title>
    <text>
        <english><![CDATA[Register now and SAVE! ]]></english>
<french><![CDATA[Inscrivez-vous maintenant et SAVE!]]></french>
    </text>
    <text>
        <english><![CDATA[Renew your commitment to our historic journey and join us for The Ride on June 9-10, 2018 at the discounted rate of just $25! Not only will you have secured your place in history for next year, but you’ll be able to pick up your commemorative 2017 long sleeve t-shirt on Saturday morning!]]></english>
		<french><![CDATA[Renouvelez votre engagement envers notre voyage historique et rejoignez-nous pour notre Année 10e Célébration sur Juin 10-11 , 2017 au tarif réduit de seulement 25$! Non seulement vous aurez obtenu votre place dans l'histoire pour l'année prochaine , mais vous serez en mesure de ramasser votre t -shirt 2017 à manches longues commémorative le samedi matin !]]></french>
    </text>
    <text>
        <english><![CDATA[Go the extra distance and become a Conqueror by making a donation of $250 with your 2018 registration. Conquerors receive a limited edition 2018 Conqueror wristband recognizing your EPIC contribution.]]></english>
<french><![CDATA[Allez la distance supplémentaire et devenir un conquérant en faisant un don de 100 $ à votre inscription 2017. Conquerors reçoivent une édition limitée 2017 Conquérant bracelet en reconnaissant votre contribution EPIC .]]></french>
    </text>
    <text>
        <english><![CDATA[If you choose to Pre-Register now and have met your fundraising minimum, the payment link will appear after choosing 'YES' and clicking the 'NEXT' button.]]></english>
<french><![CDATA[Si vous choisissez de pré- inscrire maintenant et avez rencontré votre collecte de fonds minimale , le lien de paiement apparaîtra après avoir choisi «OUI» et en cliquant sur le bouton «Suivant».]]></french>
    </text>
    <text>
        <english><![CDATA[Register for 2018 for $25]]></english>
		<french><![CDATA[Register for 2018 for $25]]></french>
    </text>
    <text>
        <english><![CDATA[Register as a Speedster with a self-donation of $100 and your registration fee will only be $15]]></english>
		<french><![CDATA[Register as a Speedster with a self-donation of $100 and your registration fee will only be $15]]></french>
    </text>
    <text>
        <english><![CDATA[Register as a Conqueror with a self-donation of $250 and we’ll waive your registration fee]]></english>
<french><![CDATA[Register as a Conqueror with a self-donation of $250 and we’ll waive your registration fee]]></french>
    </text>
    <text>
        <english><![CDATA[No thanks, I don’t want to register at this time.]]></english>
		<french><![CDATA[Non merci, je ne veux pas vous inscrire à ce moment .]]></french>
    </text>
</step>
