<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--*********************************************************************
 * @author	Kingsley U. Uwode II, contractor via Robert Half Technologies
 * @since	May 28 2015
 * @link	mailto:kingzmeadow@hotmail.com
 *
 * step_01
 * Welcome Screen (*.html view companion file)
 *-->

<step id="01">
    <page_title>
        <english><![CDATA[Welcome to Online Check-In!]]></english>
        <french><![CDATA[Bienvenue à l'enregistrement en ligne !]]></french>
    </page_title>
    <text>
        <english><![CDATA[Welcome to Online Check-In!]]></english>
        <french><![CDATA[Bienvenue à Online Check-In!]]></french>
    </text>
    <text>
        <english><![CDATA[This automated check-in process is designed to save you time and make event check-in easier than ever!  Here is what you'll need to do:]]></english>
        <french><![CDATA[Ce processus d'enregistrement automatisé est conçu pour vous faire gagner du temps et de faire événement check-in plus facile que jamais ! Voici ce que vous devez faire :]]></french>
    </text>
    <text>
        <english><![CDATA[Review your online profile.]]></english>
        <french><![CDATA[Passez en revue votre profil en ligne .]]></french>
    </text>
    <text>
        <english><![CDATA[Enter emergency contact information.]]></english>
        <french><![CDATA[Entrez les informations de contact d'urgence .]]></french>
    </text>
    <text>
        <english><![CDATA[Watch a safety video.]]></english>
        <french><![CDATA[Regarder une vidéo de sécurité .]]></french>
    </text>
    <text>
        <english><![CDATA[Use your credit card to make an instant or delayed self-pledge if you have not reached the fundraising minimum.]]></english>
        <french><![CDATA[Utilisez votre carte de crédit pour faire un auto- engagement instantané ou retardé si vous ne l'avez pas atteint le minimum de collecte de fonds .]]></french>
    </text>
    <text>
        <english><![CDATA[]]></english>
        <french><![CDATA[]]></french>
    </text>
    <text>
        <english><![CDATA[Your event material will be mailed to you if you complete Online Check-In be May 29th, 2017. After this time, your event materials will be available for pick-up onsite on Saturday morning, June 10th.]]></english>
        <french><![CDATA[Votre matériel d'événements seront envoyés à vous si vous avez terminé l'enregistrement en ligne de 7 Juin , 2016. Après cette période, vos documents d'événements seront disponibles pour le ramassage sur place le samedi matin 11ème Juin .]]></french>
    </text>
    <text>
        <english><![CDATA[We are only able to mail check-in packets to Canadian addresses.  If you live outside Canada, your packet will be available for easy pick-up on Saturday morning.]]></english>
        <french><![CDATA[Nous ne pouvons envoyer des paquets check -in aux adresses canadiennes . Si vous habitez à l'extérieur du Canada , votre paquet sera disponible pour faciliter pick-up le samedi matin ]]></french>
    </text>
    <text>
        <english><![CDATA[CREW ONLY: Your packet will be available at the All Crew Meeting on Friday, June 9th at 6:00pm both in Toronto and in Niagara]]></english>
        <french><![CDATA[]]></french>
    </text>
    <text>
        <english><![CDATA[]]></english>
        <french><![CDATA[]]></french>
    </text>
    <text>
        <english><![CDATA[]]></english>
        <french><![CDATA[]]></french>
    </text>
</step>
